Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: Media Access Copies
  - Subseries C: Sound recording Access Copies
    - "A) Silkworm, Tim B) Silkworm, Tim, Andy", undated (Case 157.0216)
    - "A) Bis B) Todd Verow", 1992 (Case 157.0218)
      Duration: A) 15 minutes B) 40 minutes
    - "Tamra's Interview", undated (Case 157.0220)
- Oversize Series I.B: I Was A Teenage Serial Killer - Production Materials
  Scope and Content Note
  Contains material related to the production of I Was A Teenage Serial Killer.
  - Promotional Material
    - Serial Killer: T-shirt, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22A)
- Oversize Series II.A: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore - Production Materials
  Contains material related to the production of Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore.
  - Production Material
    - Mary-Jane: Stage Prop, Talking Pee Wee Herman Doll, 1987 (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_e99ea2df907a80b9420124c07b624d4a)
- Oversize Series II.B: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore - Distribution and Public Relations
  Contains material related to promotion of Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore.
  - Promotional Material
    - Mary Jane: T-shirt, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 90A)
- Oversize Series IV.D: Professional Projects - Hardcorn
  Contains material related to Hardcorn Comics.
  - Promotional Material
    - Hardcorn: T-shirt, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 186)
- Oversize Series IX: Nostalgia, Neat Things
  Contains oversize material related to Series IX, "Nostalgia, Neat Things. Items include newspaper clippings, artifacts and photo albums. Arranged chronologically and by format.
  - Photo Album and Scrapbook, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 393)
  - Photo Album and Scrapbook, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 394)
  - Photo Album and Scrapbook, 1989-1997 (Box 9, Folder 395)
  - New York Times, November 26, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - San Francisco Examiner, April 20, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, May 1, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - San Francisco Examiner, June 3, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - San Francisco Examiner, November 4, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 400)
  - "1993/1994, Early Writings" clippings (Box 10, Folder 401)
  - Nightmare Before Christmas, bag, Undated (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Arlo Guthrie Poster, Undated (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Nightmare Before Christmas Kaleidoscope, Undated (Box 11)
- Oversize Series X: Miscellaneous
  Oversize miscellaneous items.
  - Wall Calendar, 1995 (Box 10)
- Accretion 2008 - Series I: I Was A Teenage Serial Killer, 1993-2000
  - Subseries A: Production Materials, 1992
    - Photo Stills, Contact Sheet, Photo Negatives, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Press and Distribution, 1993-1996
    - Press Pack Materials, 1993-1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Distribution Correspondence, K Records, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Video Sleeves, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Distribution Invoices, InSound, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Distribution Correspondence, Skura Intercontinental Trading Co., 2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: Media Originals
    Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - "I Was A Teenage Serial Killer", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0371, Case 157.0371)
      Format: Mini DV, Donated Element
    - "I Was A Teenage Serial Killer MPR Radio Interview, Sarah Jacobson 8-6-93", 1993 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0489)
    - "I Was A Teenage Serial Killer", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0490)
    - "Sarah + Beth Friend MPR Radio Interview 'I Was Teenage' 8/7/93", 1993 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0496)
- Accretion 2008 - Series II: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore, 1994-2006
  - Subseries A: Production Materials, 1994-2006
    - Investor Agreements, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Crew Deal Memorandum, Heidi M. Smith, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Mary Jane Script, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Mary Jane's Not A Script Anymore" - Shooting Script, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Photo Contract, Viviane Oh, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets + Negatives, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Slides, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Dream Wedding Photo Negatives, circa 1995 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - On-Set Photos, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - M.J. Prop List, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Saul Zaentz Company Film Center Agreement, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Sound Budgets, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Sound Invoice, Poolside Studios, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Music Supervisor Agreements and Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Soundtrack Materials, Azalia Snail, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Soundtrack Materials, Babes in Toyland, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Soundtrack Materials, The Loudmouths, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Soundtrack Materials, New Wet Kojak, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Soundtrack Materials, Steel Pole Bath Tub, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Trailer Script, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - MJ Opticals, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - "Scenes For Each Movie" Plan, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Print Invoices, Fotokem, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Timing Notes, 4MC Labs, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Subseries B: Distribution and Public Relations, 1996-2006
    - "Sarah Jacobson on the Set of Mary Jane" by Lee Jacobson, Photo and Negative, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Photo Negatives, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Press Pack Materials, Selected Press and Interviews, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Press Zine Materials, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Artist Information, Chank, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Screening Poster Materials and "Virgin" Stickers, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Website Correspondence, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Video Covers, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Distribution Summary, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Invoices and Correspondence, Canyon Cinema, 2002-2006 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, Dieter Kosslick, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, Margaret Herrick Library, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Subseries C: Media Originals
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Dub, Audio: 1 & 2 Mono, 1995 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0354)
      Format: BetaCam SP, Donated Element
      TRT: 00:06:15
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Dub, Part One, 1996 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0355)
      TRT: 00:52:00
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Dub, Part Two, 1996 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0356)
      TRT: 00:46:00
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Telecine Print Xfer, Tape #1, 1996 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0357)
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Telecine Print Xfer, Tape #2, 1996 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0358)
    - Mary Jane Is Not a Virgin Anymore Film-to-Tape Transfer @ 24 fps, 1996 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0359)
      Format: Digital BetaCam, Donated Element
      TRT: 01:38:00
    - "Mary Jane Music", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0360)
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Mono Copy R1 + R2, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0373)
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Mono Copy R3 + R4, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0374)
    - "MJ 2", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0375)
    - "MJ 3", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0376)
    - Mary Jane "Multi-Track Audio," Foley R - 1 + 2, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0377)
    - Mary Jane "Multi-Track Audio," Foley R - 3 + 4, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0378)
    - "Mary Jane Movie Audio", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0488)
    - "Artifacts on KFAI-FM, Hosted by Marya Morstad, Interview: 'Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore' - Sarah Jacobson, 2-14-97", 1997 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0497)
  - Subseries F: Objects, Props - Smiley Face Collection
    - Large Smiley Face Plush with "Smile" Ribbon, Undated (Box 25, Object ID: 157.2.0001)
    - Large Plastic Smiley Face, Undated (Box 25, Object ID: 157.2.0002)
    - Large Smiley Face Tin Wastebasket, Undated (Box 25, Object ID: 157.2.0003)
    - Ben Geffen Smiley Face Address Labels, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0004)
      Biographical/Historical Note
      Ben Geffen is Sarah Jacobson's friend from New York, who now lives in Seattle, WA. He collected most of the Smiley Face Collection.
    - Ben Geffen Smiley Face Address Label Collage, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0005)
    - Mr. Happy by Roger Hargreaves, 1980 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0006)
    - Mr. Happy Small Plush Pouch, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0007)
    - Trio of Smiley Face Plastic Balloons, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0008)
    - Smiley Face Ribbon, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0009)
    - Smiley Face Lunch Mates Bag, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0010)
    - Smiley Face Rectangular Patch, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0011)
    - Freedom Foursquare Church Prayer Card, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0012)
    - "Smile Jesus Loves You" Miniature Pamphlet, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0013)
    - "Try God" Miniature Pamphlet, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0014)
    - MAD Magazine, No. 150, April 1972 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0015)
    - Assorted Smiley Face Buttons and Pendants, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0016)
    - Smiley Face Rain Poncho, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0017)
    - Smiley Face Hand Mirror, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0018)
    - Smiley Face Fancy Nails Set, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0019)
    - "Have A Nice Day" Wire Hanger, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0020)
    - Pair of Bendy Figurines, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.0021)
    - Bright Pink Smiley Face Plush Keyring, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0022)
    - Red Smiley Face Eyewear Case, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0023)
    - Blue Smiley Face Eyewear Case, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0024)
    - Trio of Smiley Face Rubber Stamps, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0025)
    - Wind-Up Smiley Face Toy, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0026)
    - Smiley Face Night Light, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0027)
    - Smiley Face Golf Ball, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0028)
    - Smiley Face Rock, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0029)
    - Smiley Face Inflatable, Undated (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0030)
    - Trio of "Have A Happy Day" Plastic Yellow Cups, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0031)
    - Single "Have A Happy Day" Plastic Yellow Mug, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0032)
    - Blue and White Smiley Face Mug, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0033)
    - Black and Yellow Smiley Face Mug, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0034)
    - Orange and Black Smiley Face Mug, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0035)
    - Yellow Smiley Face Ceramic Mug, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0036)
    - White and Green Smiley Face Glass Mug, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0037)
    - Smiley Face Glass Goblet, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0038)
    - Smiley Face Plastic Flower Knick-Knack, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0039)
    - Smiley Face Salt & Pepper Set, 1995 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0040)
    - Pair of Smiley Face Plastic Yellow Plates, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0041)
    - "Have A Happy Day" Plastic Yellow Miniature Tray, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0042)
    - "Have A Happy Day" Red and Yellow Smiley Face Alarm Clock, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0043)
    - "Have A Happy Day" White and Yellow Wall Clock, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0044)
    - Large Yellow Smiley Face Foot Scale, Undated (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0045)
    - Large Smiley Face Tin Tray, Undated (Object ID: 157.2.0046)
    - Large Smiley Face Tin Tray with "Have a Nice Day", Undated (Object ID: 157.2.0047)
    - Bread Box Bakery Discount Store, "Have a Happy Day!!" Smiley Face Book Dusk Jacket, 1975 (Box 24, Object ID: 157.2.0048)
- Accretion 2008 - Series III: The Stains Documentary, 1980-1999
  - Subseries A: Production Materials, 1980-1999
    - Interviews and Correspondence, Nancy Dowd, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Notes and Contact Information, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - "Ladies and Gentlemen..." Photo Stills, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Subseries B: Media Originals
    Conditions Governings Access
    - "Ladies + Gentlemen, The Fabulous Stains, Tape #1", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0361)
    - "Ladies + Gentlemen, The Fabulous Stains, Tape #2", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0362)
    - "Misc. Film Clips - Stains ", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0363)
    - "Behind the Movie: The Fabulous Stains", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0379, Box Digitized Access Copies, File 157.0379)
      TRT: 00:15:00
    - "Stains - CUFF", 1997-1998 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.038, Box 11)
      Format: Hi 8 Video, Donated Element
    - "Stains Interviews - Beat Kitchen", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0381)
- Accretion 2008 - Series IV: Professional Projects
  - Subseries A: Station Wagon Productions, 1993-2006
    - Catalog, Undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Distribution Notebook, 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Budgets, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Grants, 1993-1999 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Fundraising, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Check Stubs, 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Better Property Managment Lease, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Production Invoices, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Wells Fargo Statements, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Tax Returns, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Tax Returns, Budget Duplicates, 1993-1996 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Income Tax Returns, 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - "Finance - Tax Things", 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - "My Film Stuff" - Screening and Festival Materials, 1993-2003 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - "New Website" Note, Undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Crossroads Films Press Release, Undated (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Photos of Sarah and Ruth by Julie Pavlowski, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Station Wagon Productions Business Cards, Undated (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Contacts, Business Cards, Undated (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Mailing Lists, Undated (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence 1, 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence 2, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Correspondence 3, 1999-2005 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Unmailed Correspondence by Sarah, Undated (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Film II Ledger Notebook, Undated (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Subseries B: Sleaze, 1995-2003
    - Babes in Toyland Press, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - "Chicks in Rock" Collected Press Clips, 1980-2002 (Box 19, Folder 73A)
    - Sleaze Scrapbook Materials 1 of 2, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Sleaze Scrapbook Materials 2 of 2, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Sleaze Scrapbook, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Sleaze Plot Synopsis and Summary, Undated (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Sleaze Script, Undated (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - "Sleaze Script With Jim's Notes", Undated (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - "Questions for Possible Producers" and To-Do List for Andrea Sperlinge, Undated (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - "Power Revision" by Robert E. Byrd, Scr(i)pt Mag, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Sleaze Rockefeller Proposal, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Sleaze "Sneak Peak" Event, Sneak Preview Entertainment and Fifth Night, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Notebook, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Notebook, Undated (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Production Agreement and Script Notes, Mark J. Huisman, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - "Sleaze Notes", Undated (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - "Matt's Sleaze Notes", 2003 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Soundtrack List, Undated (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - "Sleaze Receipts", 2002 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - Sleaze Copyright Information, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Subseries C: The Adventures of Sweet Miss: The Disco Years, 1988
    - Sweet Miss Production Materials, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Subseries E: Film Festivals and Concerts, 1999
    - 6th Annual Chicago Underground Film Festival Program, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Subseries F: VH1, 2001-2003
    - Radical Cheerleaders Materials and Research, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Subseries G: Oxygen Media, 1999-2000
    - Offer of Employment, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - Correspondence, Woodstock "Rapestock/Hellstock", 1999 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - Correspondence, Sneak Preview, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - Recommendation for Lauren Monocell, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Subseries H: 50/50, 2000-2005
    - STIGMA Manifesto, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Alice Locas Materials, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Subseries I: Writing Files, 1988-2003
    - "Sarah's Novel," Book 1 of 2, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 102)
    - "Sarah's Novel," Book 2 of 2, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 103)
    - Resumes and Biography, 1990-2003 (Box 20, Folder 104)
    - Cover Letters, 2000-2003 (Box 20, Folder 105)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Unedited Interviews, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 106)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Edited Interviews, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 107)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Introduction, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 108)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Draft, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 109)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Published Version, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 110)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 111)
    - "Dry", 1993 (Box 20, Folder 112)
    - "Sex At the Movies" A Screenplay by Sarah Jacobson, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 113)
    - Freelance Writing, Published Articles, 1996-2001 (Box 20, Folder 114)
    - "Old Projects, Outlines", 1999-2002 (Box 20, Folder 115)
    - Playboy, Freelance Drafts, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 116)
    - Pitches and Proposals, 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 117)
    - IFC Teen Film Pitch, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 118)
    - Script Proposals, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 119)
    - Freelance Drafts, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 120)
    - "Old Projects: Blackout Books Log", 2000 (Box 20, Folder 121)
    - YM Magazine Rosewood Prison Research, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 122)
    - YM Magazine Rosewood Prison Consent Forms, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 123)
    - YM Magazine Rosewood Prison Article Notebook, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 124)
    - "High School Reunion" Production Materials, 1988-2002; This file includes objects related to Sarah Jacobson's Edina High School experience, including a letterman patch and photographs. (Box 20, Folder 125)
    - "High School Reunion" Synopsis and Biography, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    - Much Music, "Adam Tastemaker" Schedule, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 127)
    - "Popular Is Hell" Research, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 128)
    - "Rock 'n Roll Parking Lot" Production Bid Paperwork, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 129)
    - "Backtracks" TV Proposal and Production Materials, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 130)
    - Freelance Writing, Correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 131)
    - "Goals for 2002" (Box 20, Folder 132)
    - "Celebrity High School Reunion" Pitch, Undated (Box 20, Folder 133)
    - "Puppetistas" Notes, Undated (Box 20, Media 134)
    - U MTV Notes, Undated (Box 20, Folder 135)
    - "Freakathon" Scrapbook Materials 1 of 2, Undated (Box 20, Folder 136)
    - "Freakathon" Scrapbook Materials 2 of 2, Undated (Box 20, Folder 137)
    - "Freakathon" Research, Magic and Circuses, Undated (Box 20, Folder 138)
    - "Freakathon" Research, Vacation/Resorts, Undated (Box 20, Folder 139)
    - "Freakathon" Notes and Script, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 140)
    - "Music," Lyrics and Notation, Undated (Box 20, Folder 141)
    - "Sarah's Songs", Undated (Box 20, Folder 142)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 143)
    - Notebook, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 144)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 145)
    - Notebook, "Sundance", 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 146)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 147)
    - Notebook, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 148)
    - Day to Day To-Do Lists, Prep for Interviews, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 149)
    - Notebook, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 150)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 151)
    - Notebook, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 152)
    - Notebook, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 153)
    - Notebook, circa 2000 (Box 21, Folder 154)
    - Notebook, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 155)
    - "Sarah - Living on 16th St. NY" Notebook, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 156)
    - Notebook, circa 2002 (Box 21, Folder 157)
    - Notebook, circa 2002 (Box 21, Folder 158)
  - Subseries J: Media Originals
    Subseries J contains donated media elements related to the previous subseries. Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - "Sarah's Films" - [1] Making of the Diner / Diner Video [2] What I Learned In A Buick Station Wagon / Road Movie [3] Disco Film [4] Java Jive [5] Eiffel Tower High, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0315)
    - "Sarah's Films for the Family" - [1] The Making of the Diner Scene from Road Movie [2] Road Movie (or What I Learned in a Buick Station Wagon) [3] The Adventures of Sweet Miss The Disco Years [4] Film for Mom [5] Eiffel Tower High, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0316)
    - "Road Movie, What I Learned in a Buick Station Wagon", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0372)
    - "Wild Sound for What I Learned", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0492)
    - "The Adventures of Sweet Miss The Disco Years", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0397)
    - "Eiffel Tower High", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0339)
    - "Rough Cut Films on Video" - [1] Sweet Miss [2] Paula Gotlesman's NY, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0349)
    - "Sleaze Auditions 3/00", 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0317)
    - "Sleaze, Tape # 1", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0382)
    - "Sleaze, Tape #2", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0383)
    - "Sleaze, Tape #3", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0384)
      Format: DV Cam, Donated Element
    - "Sleaze Soundtrack - Tape #1", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0480)
    - "Sleaze Soundtrack - Tape #2", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0481)
    - "Sleaze, 5th Night Reading 4/11/00", 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0482)
    - "Sarah Jacobson Music Video Reel" [1] Man or Astroman - Sferic Waves [2] The Jack Saints - Brain Bats from Venus [3] Fluffy - Vomit [4] Mary Jane Trailer, Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0368)
      Format: Video Cassette, Donated Element
    - "Man or Astroman Spferic Waves Music Video", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0392)
    - "The Jack Saints Video - Brain Brats From Venus, Master", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0341)
    - "Fluffy: Music Video", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0459)
    - "Reunion #2 8/99", 1999 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0431)
    - "Reunion #3 8/99", 1999 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0432)
    - "High School Reunion", Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0435, Case 157.0435)
    - "Sarah Jacobson Director's Reel" - [1] "Sferic Waves" - Man or Astroman? [2] "Teenage Serial Killer" - film excerpt [3] "Vomit" - Fluffy [4] "Mary Jane's Not a Virgin" - film excerpt, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0364)
      TRT: 00:10:00
    - "Sarah Jacobson Producer/Writer 2/2003" (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0365)
    - "Sarah's Reel" / Sarah Jacobson Producer/Writer Reel 2-19-03 - [1] Cecil B. Demented [2] Playing for Peanuts [3] Phantom Planet [4] Adam [5] Summer Concert [6] Stains, 2003 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0402)
    - "TV Moments Segments" / "My 100 Greatest TV Moments", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0328)
    - "Sarah's 100 TV Moments Segments" - [1] #99 Cop Rock, #96 Public Image Limited on Bandstand, #93 Courtney [2] #35 Charlie Brown Christmas, #30 Bowie and Bing [3] #21 Homerpallooza [4] #46 Lennon/Cosell, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0366)
    - "100 TV Moments Segments for VH1", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0391)
    - "Paul Cook Interview 5-8-98", 1998 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0369)
    - "Paul Cook", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0370)
    - "My First Time," Women Directors' First Films, Tamra Davis, Esther Bell, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0347)